[
  {
    "question": "What is the value of PI",
    "correct_answer": "3.14",
    "incorrect_answers": [ "3.12", "1.58", "6.28"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who and when invented PI",
    "correct_answer": "William Jones in 1706",
    "incorrect_answers": [" ", " ", " "]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the cube of 7",
    "correct_answer": " 343",
    "incorrect_answers": ["216 ", " 215", "516"]
  },
  {
    "question": "I am an odd number. Take away one letter and I become even. What number am I?",
    "correct_answer": "Seven",
    "incorrect_answers": [" Six", " Five", " one"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Sally is 54 years old and her mother is 80, how many years ago was Sallyâ€™s mother times her age?",
    "correct_answer": "41 ",
    "incorrect_answers": [" 39", " 64", " 85"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is a liner equation from the following",
    "correct_answer": "2x=6",
    "incorrect_answers": ["2x^2=8", "8x^4=160", " 5b^3=200"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If 2 = 5, then what is the answer of (2*5-2)",
    "correct_answer": "23",
    "incorrect_answers": [" 10", "8 ", "12"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which value is greater than 4",
    "correct_answer": "5",
    "incorrect_answers": ["-1/2", "-25", "-4"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the smallest",
    "correct_answer": "-1",
    "incorrect_answers": [ "-1/2", "0", "3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Find the missing terms in multiple of 3: 3, 6, 9, __, 15",
    "correct_answer": "12",
    "incorrect_answers": [ "11", "13", "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "50 times of 8 is equal to",
    "correct_answer": "400",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "448", "470", "800"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 130+125+191",
    "correct_answer": "446",
    "incorrect_answers": ["448", "470", "783"]
  }
]
